natively.com 2010-02-08

# About Natively.com - Privacy Policy

(Last updated December 11, 2008)

Privacy Protection Commitment by Natively.com  
Natively.com is obliged to protect the privacy of its clients. This obligation is, as mentioned, subject to changes and  
updates from time to time - you are therefore required to check in from time to time.

At purchasing time, Natively Academy gathers information such as the user's age range, gender,  
country, zip code, e-mail address and general interests.  
The purpose of gathering this information is to help Natively Academy provide better service to  
our users and aggregate information to third parties interested in usage patterns of different demographic groups.  
Natively Academy may share information about users with business partners, sponsors and other third parties; however,  
we do so only in the aggregate and never on a personal basis.

Natively Academy checks for the following information when using Natively Academy software:  
your operating system, Natively Academy Software version, browser version, connectivity, and information regarding  
your use and the configuration of the Natively Academy Software ("Parameters"). Parameters are collected in order to  
provide you with the Software and Services subject to the provisions hereof;

Payment Collection Information  
when purchasing a subscription using your credit card, you will be asked to submit data such as the credit card number.  
Natively.com uses the most updated information security technology, whose purpose is to protect your credit card details  
during the transmission of data stored on the servers. This SSL technology ('Secure Sockets Layers'), secures billions of  
dollars' worth of transactions over the internet. Natively.com uses a mediator for the purpose of clearing all credit card  
transactions.

Additional Information Collected  
When contacting Natively.com through the 'Contact' option, we use the submitted information and email address to  
answer questions or problems concerning the Nativeky.com site. Additionally, some information (such as IP address,  
browser, computer type and operating system) is stored automatically. This kind of information helps us answer your  
questions, especially those concerning technical difficulties. Filing such information concerning content allows diagnosis  
of problems related to our servers, security management and demographic attribution. We also collect such information  
at times for internal business needs that are not accessible to anyone outside Natively.com. We will disclose this  
information only if required to do so by law.

Security  
We use 'Cookies' in order to simplify the user's experience. You can set your browser preferences to a 'cookie' rejecting  
mode, but be advised that the service may not function properly then. Natively.com data is stored behind 'Firewalls' so  
as to prevent loss, changing or misuse of information under our control. We have adopted preventive tools that limit  
access to sensitive information, and that locates and prevents access plus certain actions from unauthorized users.  
While these means exceed the industry standards, no complaint has been raised as for the penetrability of our system at  
exceptional cases, or concerning its ability to withstand malicious attempts in the future.

Links  
Natively.com includes links to different sites. Please note that when 'clicking' any of these links, you are 'clicking' another  
site. We request that you read the Privacy Protection Notice on these sites, since theirs may differ from ours.

Personally Identifiable Information  
Usafis Organization may provide your email information to selected partners, reputable companies or organizations  
whose products and services may interest you. If Usafis Organization discloses personally identifiable information to  
third-party companies who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or  
block such uses. In addition, Usafis Organization may share personally identifiable information with selected 3rd parties,  
and may utilize the services of 3rd party marketing partners to combine additional information from these 3rd parties with  
the collected personal information. These 3rd parties may send you offers via online marketing. If you prefer not to  
receive online marketing information from Usafis Organization or third-party companies, please contact online.

Opt-out  
Natively.com sends messages to its subscribers via email from time to time, concerning new services, improvements,  
notice of scheduled services etc. Our subscribers may choose not to receive this information by suspending their  
subscription with us.

Notifications Regarding Changes  
In the event of a fundamental change in our privacy protection policy or in the manner we use your personal information,  
we will make sure to post a notification on our website 30 days earlier.

Contacting the Site  
You may address any question you may have regarding this document, the site policy or the way you use the site by  
contacting Natively.com, using the 'Contact' link.
